Copyright and Trademarks
Microsoft®, Windows® and Microsoft Internet Explorer® are registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation.
Mac OS, Bonjour and AppleTalk are registered trademarks of Apple Computer, Inc.
General Notice: Other product names used herein are for identification purposes only and may be trademarks of their respective owners. Epson disclaims any and all rights in those marks.
Copyright (C) Seiko Epson Corporation 2004-2018. All rights reserved.
